(Director:)Yeah, but. ..
(Leonard:)...there was ample parking.
(Penny:)Are you done?
(Leonard:)And you were so good
in the TV commercial.
It was for hemorrhoid cream.
(Leonard:)And I got itchy and swollen
just watching you.
(Penny:)Leonard, you are really
not cheering me up.
(Leonard:)Come on. How can you be sad
when you're going home
(Leonard:)with all five-foot-six of this?
(Penny:)You think you're five-foot-six,
that's funny.
(Raj:)I don't understand it.
(Raj:)I'm a nice guy, I have a great job,
(Raj:)I'm well-educated,
come from a good family...
(Raj:)Why don't women want to be with me?
(Sheldon:)An interesting question.
(Sheldon:)Well... good night.
(Raj:)What? Don't send me home.
I can't be alone right now.
(Sheldon:)That's your problem.
You can't be alone.